I am my child, my proud daughter of Richard Ganim.
It is Trina's honor to accept this recognition on my father's new life.
And I am sorry that due to his ill health, he is not present tonight.
We would like to thank Debbie and Dan Hansen for all the work they did this
evening.
We would like to thank Mr. Pierre Jane for his kind words, his friendship, not
just tonight, but for many, many years.
Thank you to my father's Lebanese friends, American friends, church friends,
city officials friends for being here tonight.
And father and his proud to be Lebanese, but more so he is proud to be an
American.
He loves this country, he has served this country, he believes in three
principles.
You serve your God, you serve your family, you serve your country. He has done
all three probably.
As Mr. Janey said, he grew up here in America with immigrant parents.
He has been a lifelong member of St. Aaron, Aaron High Catholic Church.
And he loves his church, he has loved it since the day he was born.
He continues to love it and when he is able to, he attends the church regularly
there.
He has done a lesson to all of us, diversity, love everyone, love those who are
different from you, learn what they are about, learn different faiths, learn
different cultures.
Because he really believed that if we learned and we educated ourselves, then
that is what we would do, we would get along, we would be at peace with one
another.
And that's what he tried to do in his life.
I know as a child growing up, my father loved this country as I said.
And he served it well, both in the World War II and then coming home and
serving the city of Seven Hills.
He loved politics. He thrived on it.
And along with minor George, he started cameo, an organization that to this day
still thrives.
So I would like to congratulate those who are also getting inducted along with
my father.
He is humbled to be included in such a district, the distinguished class, and I
once again regret that he is unable to attend tonight.
[APPLAUSE]